

GAME PROGRAMMER

Details

Gdańsk

Poland

grzpotry@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Polish

DATE OF BIRTH

1995

Links

Github

Skills

Unity / C#

Unreal Engine / C++

Continous Integration (Jenkins/TeamCity)

Languages

Polish (native)

English (fluent)

Hobbies

Science, Astrophysics, Outdoor, Scuba-Diving, Hiking, Videography, Triathlon, Sci-Fi

Profile

Over 8 years of experience in game software development as programmer. 8 years in Unity and 2 years in Unreal Engine on which I am now mostly focused on.

With a wealth of experience in transforming design concepts into gameplay, I thrive when tackling new challenges and realizing ambitious visions.

Consider myself as generalist - extensive experience in a rapidly growing studio required wearing many hats and engaging in various phases of the production, from concept, through rough development - to the final releases and product maintenance.

Employment History

Unity Programmer - Tower of Time, Event Horizon

MAY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

https://store.steampowered.com/app/617480/Tower_of_Time/

Tower of Time was first project in game dev I've worked on in newly emerging game studio Event Horizon. During that time I was still studying on University so it was part-time job mostly. I was chiefly responsible for gameplay programming and tools in small team of 4 programmers.

Senior Unity Programmer - Dark Envoy, Event Horizon

OCTOBER 2019 - JANUARY 2024

https://store.steampowered.com/app/945770/Dark_Envoy/

After successful launch of Tower of Time, I started to worked on more ambitious RPG title with multiplayer co-op, procedural content generation, cinematic in-game cutscenes, voice over and much deeper rpg progression mechanics.

Chief technical areas of expertise in this project

- Developed Procedural Content Generation systems (dungeons, loot, quests etc.)
- Leaded enemies AI development, prepared BT tools used by designers
- Integrated and supervised 3rd party tools (eg. visual scripting) for designers
- Collaborated on core combat and quests mechanics
- Supported development of multiplayer features
- Automated build, and testing pipelines by utilizing CI system (jenkins)
- Optimized application performance (CPU, memory, loadings)

Unreal Engine Programmer - Survive the Fall, Angry Bulls Studio

OCTOBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Small part-time order at the early stage of Survive the Fall development.

Unreal Engine Programmer - Unannounced Project, Event Horizon

FEBRUARY 2024 - PRESENT

Currently I work on unannounced action RPG in Unreal Engine 5 heavily based on Lyra and GAS (C++ and blueprints) with automation shifted from Jenkins to TeamCity.

Education

Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Gdańsk University of Technology

OCTOBER 2014 - FEBRUARY 2018